[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this last night"]}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "You as a high profile gay black man, I mean what is your reaction to this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well we, Piers as you know, we just covered this last night, what exactly is free speech to me really have free speech in this country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Why did you hug your teacher?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I hug all my teachers just to show appreciation on what they do from me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "And have you hugged this teacher before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Yes plenty of time 4 to 5 times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Four to 5 times and other teachers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, just a few (ph) even if they haven't teach and taught me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "This particular teacher apparently says that she warned you not to hug her is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Did other students hug the teachers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Yeah, other students hug teachers -- other teachers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "You don't think there's anything inappropriate about what you did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "No, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Are you mischievous how do you describe yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I mean, I describe my self as a well-mannered man and I'm basically about to be 18 so I'm well on my way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "She apparently said in the discipline report that your lips touched the back of her neck and chick did they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "No sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "I mean what was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I was just thinking about senior year and what am I going to do for my education, like my heart dropped like I didn't know what to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "CC", "WP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Has it stopped you hugging people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "In a sense, I feel more cautious and what -- how I go about greeting people and if they -- if I do go at least hesitate for -- just like oh, wait no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "And (inaudible) is there any leave of appeal here, do you got any last recourse to try and get this changed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "``", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well the appeal has been sent in today, so we have to wait for the board to make a decision on are they going to reinstate him along back in school.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP"], "qSentId": 131, "question": "I hope the school see sense because your pretty good sportsman, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Yes sir", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "So they think you're back in the team?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Definitely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "But just to clarify are you saying that your client did pay this housekeeper the minimum wage or above?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "She paid this housekeeper exactly what she promised to pay her well above the minimum wage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "It did seem absolutely crazy, is that true, did that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Well, that's exactly what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "I mean, have you talked to your client directly about that particular part of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "I've spent an enormous amount of time with my client and just to set the record straight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["India"]}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "What was it the journalist asked you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Because the journalist was asking me to keep quiet about something that I've been so passionate about and the problem in India of this gang rape.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Has it reinforce your view that things must change in India?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["India"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "How do you feel about the fact that you have no relationship with your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "I think father's blessings are very important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Christmas"]}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Have you heard from him at all since you had such success with films?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Really, of course were social with each other, like on occasions, like Christmas and family weddings we meet each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Sad isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "HEREWAT: Very sad, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Do you worry about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Not anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Why does your stepmother Jean (ph) have such a resistance to seeing your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "You know, there's been a resistance for so long, ever since my father married her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "A part of it is sort of absurd legal barriers we face here but how was your father when you saw him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "We're not allowed to say that either else visitations can get pulled.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "And you have grandchildren as well, any children between you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Your stepmother Jean (ph), talk to her and you tell her, what would you say to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Wow, I mean ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "What do you want to say to this person to try and make her see and let, two obviously loving children see their father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "CD", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Piers, we said everything we needed to say to her whether it's in to a camera, whether it's to you, whether it's to a judge or to our lawyers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Is she the -- let's try and play devil's advocate is part of the reason she's doing this that she doesn't want people to see your father in the condition that he's in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", ":", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "My father's biggest joy in life was his family and his friends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "You know if you could choose any song of all the songs to dedicate to your father right now, which one would you go for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Did you ever know that you're my hero.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "What was it you wanted to tell me, darling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "How would she have said that too and this isn't going to be easy to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 414, "question": "How could you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Well, it wasn't ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "How are you Tim, I mean you, when you finish this book what did you conclude about your extraordinary life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Well it -- I haven't read the book, but I understand that it's very good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "What was it like when you first began to work they realized you have this extraordinary chemistry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "It was marvelous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "What made Carol so special?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "NNP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Well she's very giving and very -- she's just wonderful, you know, its -- you can not anger her by any means.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carol"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Are you naturally like that or is it always quite hard work for you to perform?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Well I have a natural humor about me and when I talk to people that comes out, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "They've been bouncing of walls about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "And even you wouldn't know what was going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "So what -- so is that why kept cracking up so much is that you just couldn't -- you didn't know what's happening next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", ":", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "We never cracked up on purpose ever, ever, ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "RB", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "How did you get to be funny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Well, there's -- that's just -- dyslexia helped me out a lot because I would get up to read in class and I couldn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "URNETT: Did you tell Piers about the doorbell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Do you find it offensive the modern kind of way of telling pretty crude jokes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Do you dislike it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "If you -- If I say it right, you've got five minutes to live, you can tell one joke again before you peg it, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "ONWAY: I would go holdup a bank.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Do you still do stand up on the occasion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "I do a sit down now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Would you ever bank your joke a little err, if it's not going great?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "If you got one you pull out the ether?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "You don't tell jokes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Do you find everything pretty funny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "... who's a professional comedian?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Newhart is pretty funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Carol, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Well ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "You could pay to see one comedian on stage again, who would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Well, I like -- they're apples and oranges.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]